STEPHANIE UNGER

ADMINISTRATOR, MARKETER, TEAM PLAYER, INSTRUCTOR, AND ARTIST

(352) 672-1026



stephanie@ungermail.com



2010 Monterey Cir apt E, Alameda, CA 94501

Experienced arts administrator and instructor for dance companies, dance studios, an after school program, and a school-touring dance company. Specialty in marketing work, especially in communications: email, writing, and phone skills. Retail and customer service representative. Dance performer, choreographer, and director.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing Professional

2013-2024

- Freelance Marketing Specialist
- · Marketing Manager
- Social Media and Project Manager
- Email and website updates, photography and design, physical collateral, social media

Retail Supervisor and Customer Service 2007-2013

- Barista Trainer
- Shift Supervisor
- Customer Service Representative
- Team management, inventory, engaging with customers

Arts Administrator

2010-2020

- Managing Director
- Artistic Director
- · Touring and Outreach Director
- Managing grants, marketing, coordinating schedules, fundraising efforts

Childcare and Instruction 2006-2023

- Kindergarten Teacher
- · Dance Instructor
- After School Program Instuctor
- Classroom management, curriculum design, communication with parents

EDUCATION

2002-2006

University of Florida

Bachelor in English, cum laude

1998-2002 Douglas Anderson School of the Arts Graduated with honors

SKILLS

- Administrative tools: Google Suite
- Email tools: Constant Contact, Mailchimp
- Project management tools: Asana
- Communication tools: Slack
- Various marketing and design tools